{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"automehani","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"automehani","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"cvjeta","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"cvr","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"amac","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arapa","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aroban","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arobnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"arobnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"as","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"asopis","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"aša","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"avao","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekaonica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"elo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"empres","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"estitka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"esto","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešalj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ešnjak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etiri","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etkica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrdeset","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etrnaest","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverokratnik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etverokut","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvorka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"etvrtina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"inele","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"initi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ist","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ista","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ista","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"istiti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itanka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itaonica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"itav","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"izma","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"okolada","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ovjek","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uditi se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"udo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uvati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"vrst","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ćevap","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"de","osnova2":"ko","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dje","osnova2":"ji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"djevoj","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"doru","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"druk","osnova2":"iji","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"dvoto","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gimnasti","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gimnasti","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"gla","osnova2":"alo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"hla","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"igra","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ispri","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ispri","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ispri","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ivan","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ju","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kle","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"klju","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"knjižni","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kola","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"koli","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"koli","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kornja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kota","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kov","osnova2":"eg","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"krma","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kroja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"kroja","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lije","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"lopo","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ljubi","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ljulja","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mađioni","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mađioni","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"masla","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"matemati","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"matemati","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mehani","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mehani","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mjese","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mladun","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mom","osnova2":"ad","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"mu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"na","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nao","osnova2":"ale","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naran","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naru","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"naslonja","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"natika","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"natje","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nau","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepuša","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nepuša","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nov","osnova2":"anica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"nov","osnova2":"anik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"novorođen","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"njema","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"obla","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"o","osnova2":"uh","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"odlu","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ogrta","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"otklju","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"otklju","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pala","osnova2":"inka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"papu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pau","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"p","osnova2":"ela","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pisa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pješ","osnova2":"anik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pjeva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pjeva","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plesa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plesa","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pliva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pliva","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plo","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"plo","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"etak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"po","osnova2":"etnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"podru","osnova2":"je","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pokaziva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pokriva","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"politi","osnova2":"arka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"presko","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pri","osnova2":"est","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"itati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prodava","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"prodava","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"puša","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"puša","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"un","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ra","osnova2":"unalo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"raj","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"razli","osnova2":"it","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"re","osnova2":"enica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rije","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rje","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ru","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rup","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ruži","osnova2":"ast","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"savija","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sendvi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sestri","osnova2":"na","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sije","osnova2":"anj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sko","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slasti","osnova2":"arnica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sli","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slu","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"slu","osnova2":"ajnost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"ar","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sto","osnova2":"arica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"strunja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"sun","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"svira","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"svira","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"te","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tenisa","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tenisa","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"to","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tra","osnova2":"nica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tratin","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"tr","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"enica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"enik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"initi","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"ionica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"itelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iteljica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"uklju","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"uklju","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"usisava","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"uskli","osnova2":"nik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"uspinja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"era","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ve","osnova2":"erati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"velja","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vesla","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vesla","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elist","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elistica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"violon","osnova2":"elo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vje","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjen","osnova2":"anje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjen","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjerou","osnova2":"itelj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vjerou","osnova2":"iteljica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vodi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"vodi","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"voza","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"voza","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zajedni","osnova2":"ki","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zaklju","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zavi","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zna","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"zna","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ži","osnova2":"ara","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bi","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"Boži","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"boži","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"bra","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"brati","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"budu","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"cvije","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"ekić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"elav","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ćevap","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"irilica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"uk","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"","osnova2":"up","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"do","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"doma","osnova2":"in","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"došaš","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"drve","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"du","osnova2":"an","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ga","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"goš","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"i","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ispe","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"iza","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"izi","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"k","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"kozli","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"krš","osnova2":"anin","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"krš","osnova2":"anka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ku","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"le","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"le","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"liš","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"eha","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ma","osnova2":"uhica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"miši","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mladi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mo","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"mogu","osnova2":"nost","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"na","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"ak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ne","osnova2":"akinja","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"nesre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"no","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"no","osnova2":"ni","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"obu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"obu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"odje","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"omogu","osnova2":"avati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"omogu","osnova2":"iti","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"omogu","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"aj","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"osje","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"oti","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pam","osnova2":"enje","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pe","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pi","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pla","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"plu","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"polno","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pomo","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pomo","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pono","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"posje","osnova2":"ivati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pove","osnova2":"alo","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"povr","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"pro","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"prolje","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"ražnji","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"re","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["č","ć"],"osnova":"rup","osnova2":"ić","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"si","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sje","osnova2":"ati se","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sje","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sme","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"snjegovi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"spava","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"srnda","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"staja","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sti","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"stolje","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"sve","osnova2":"enik","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"svije","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"svu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"še","osnova2":"er","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"štapi","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"te","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"teku","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"teku","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tisu","osnova2":"u","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tre","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tre","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"trudno","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"tu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"u","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"uš","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"e","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"ka","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vo","osnova2":"njak","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vra","osnova2":"ati","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vre","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vrti","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"ica","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vru","osnova2":"ina","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"vu","osnova2":"i","glagol":"","pin":"",},
{"question":"popuni","hint":"č/ć","correctAnswer":["ć","č"],"osnova":"zada","osnova2":"a","glagol":"","pin":"",},
